{
    "questions": {
        "1": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1PQ3WNLwEOE5QMEFeIhvoXMMG4tt_2bPS/preview",
            "ans": "c",
            "options": [
                "40Ω",
                "20Ω",
                "30Ω",
                "10Ω"
            ]
        },
        "2": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1y8RMwSlfMEJAXr8SWqOZxl8OZFHc8e-V/preview",
            "ans": "c",
            "options": [
                "200 V",
                "250 V",
                "300 V",
                "400 V"
            ]
        },
        "3": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HfvPzE5f9UAFKgEp0Tu1U_QCdAUTdt0t/preview",
            "ans": "d",
            "options": [
                "111Ω",
                "11.1Ω",
                "9.0Ω",
                "0.9Ω"
            ]
        },
        "4": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/15nihCdt00As4AoZtC7ixaZaiXZlnwqz4/preview",
            "ans": "a",
            "options": [
                "increases, increases",
                "decreases, decreases",
                "increases, decreases",
                "decreases, increases"
            ]
        },
        "5": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1068r2nOjwea7VyPEnXpwxZG6cqvtYvAR/preview",
            "ans": "c",
            "options": [
                "539 V",
                "- 638 V",
                "-539 V",
                "438 V"
            ]
        },
        "6": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1E2b8GZAfe_ztTMuMErFMBs8iEXmy4X9Z/preview",
            "ans": "b",
            "options": [
                "F= 85 Newton",
                "F= 80 Newton",
                "F= 90 Newton",
                "F= 95 Newton"
            ]
        },
        "7": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1rR3bBGd8cDUsUopwZmXNH6PBG2F-OuUJ/preview",
            "ans": "a",
            "options": [
                "-19.2 * 10^-19 Joule",
                "-19.2 * 10^-20 Joule",
                "-19.2 * 10^-21 Joule",
                "-19.2 * 10^-22 Joule"
            ]
        },
        "8": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Ng53mXoqHYxkL9VTjPriKjA7_p0NtPUT/preview",
            "ans": "a",
            "options": [
                "Multimeter",
                "Sphygmomanometer",
                "Ahmeter",
                "Richter Scale"
            ]
        },
        "9": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1jIy5H2LEjSKOlWBQ3xQd5zqRWChApvai/preview",
            "ans": "a",
            "options": [
                "Conventional current flows from the positive terminal to the negative terminal while The electron current is the flow of negative charges or electrons through a conductor. ",
                "Conventional current is the flow of negative charges or electrons through a conductor while electron current flows from the positive terminal to the negative terminal ",
                "Both are correct",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        "10": {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1V1zd-LwRtncnGexVlCbJWBwsx5GEMIjK/preview",
            "ans": "d",
            "options": [
                "Ohm’s law states that there is an equal and opposite reaction for every action.",
                "Ohm’s law states that the total number of atoms/molecules of a gas (i.e. the amount of gaseous substance) is directly proportional to the volume occupied by the gas at constant temperature and pressure.",
                "Ohm’s law states that the pressure exerted by a gas (of a given mass, kept at a constant temperature) is inversely proportional to the volume occupied by it.",
                "Ohm’s law states that the voltage across a conductor is directly proportional to the current flowing through it, provided all physical conditions and temperature, remain constant."
            ]
        }
    }
}